By clicking Accept you agree with our [Terms of Service](https://www.freeconferencecall.com/global/gb/terms-of-service "Terms of Service") and how we collect and protect personal data. [Learn More](https://www.freeconferencecall.com/global/gb/terms-of-service "Learn More")... Accept

Have international participants? We offer local in-country dial in numbers in 70+ countries. [View list of supported countries](https://www.freeconferencecall.com/international-conferencing?country_code=gb&locale=global "View list of supported countries").

Toggle navigation [](https://www.freeconferencecall.com/?country_code=gb&locale=global "FreeConferenceCall.com")[Log In](https://www.freeconferencecall.com/global/gb/login "Log In")

Sign Up

    * Host Meeting
    * Join Meeting
    
* Host Meeting
* Join Meeting

Sign Up

* Join
* Host

Privacy Policy
==============

**Last Updated: May 22, 2018**

CarrierX, LLC ("CarrierX") is committed to respecting the privacy of all users (“users,” “you”) of our website(s) and mobile applications and the products and services available on such websites and mobile applications (collectively, the “Services”). We have established and implemented this Privacy Statement to inform you of the information we collect from you on in connection with the Services, how we collect and use your information, with whom and for what purposes we may share your information, and the choices you can make about our use of your information.

YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION MAY BE PROCESSED BY US IN THE COUNTRY WHERE IT WAS COLLECTED AS WELL AS OTHER COUNTRIES (INCLUDING THE UNITED STATES) WHERE LAWS REGARDING PROCESSING OF PERSONAL INFORMATION MAY BE LESS STRINGENT THAN THE LAWS IN YOUR COUNTRY. BY USING THE SERVICES AND PROVIDING ANY PERSONAL INFORMATION, YOU ARE CONSENTING TO THE TRANSFER OF DATA FROM YOUR COUNTRY TO A COUNTRY THAT HAS LESS STRINGENT LAWS, AND THE PROCESSING OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION IN CONFORMANCE WITH THIS POLICY.

Types of Personal Information We Collect
----------------------------------------

The phrase "Personal Information" in this Privacy Policy means contact information (e.g., name, address, email address, mailing address, telephone number) and any other information that personally identifies an individual.

In general, we collect Personal Information in connection with the provision of the Services. There are certain Services that are only provided to users who have established an account with us ("Account"). To register for an Account, we require that you provide certain Personal Information, including your name, email address, mailing address, and phone number. If you are registering for a Service that requires payment, we will also collect payment information, including (i) your name as it appears on the card; (ii) the credit card type; (iii) a valid credit card number; (iv) the date of expiration of your credit card; (v) your billing address; and (vi) any activation numbers or codes needed to charge your card.

We may also collect Personal Information about you when you sign in to a CarrierX app or website using a social networking account, such as a Facebook account. These social networking sign-in features may also enable a CarrierX account to be created more easily by using the information you provided to the social networking site. By using these sign-in features, the social networking site also will know that you have a CarrierX account. To learn more about the privacy and information collection and sharing practices of a social networking site on which you interact with CarrierX, please refer to the privacy policy for that social networking site.

We may also collect Personal Information that you submit to us voluntarily when you correspond with us or interact with the Services, such as phone device contacts. We may combine your Personal Information with information we receive offline, such as when you interact with our customer service group, or that we obtain through third party sources.

You can always decline to provide any Personal Information to us—it is your choice, and you are under no obligation to provide Personal Information to us. However, if you decide not to provide such information, then you may not be able to use or purchase the Services. At any point, you may access, review, and modify your Personal Information from your Account, or by contacting us at the number provided below.

To make a request for information we hold about you, how to request access, correct, amend or delete your Personal Data, contact: [privacy@freeconferencecall.com](mailto:privacy@freeconferencecall.com "privacy@freeconferencecall.com") or [privacy@huddle.team](mailto:privacy@huddle.team "privacy@huddle.team") or [privacy@startemeeting.com](mailto:privacy@startemeeting.com "privacy@startemeeting.com") or [privacy@bullhorn.fm](mailto:privacy@bullhorn.fm "privacy@bullhorn.fm"). Please include "My Personal Data" in the subject line. Be sure to state the reason for the request, (i.e., amend my data, port my data or purge my data), along with your name, dial-in number and access code to properly identify your account. The email must come from the registered email address on file for the account.

In-Session Information
----------------------

We may collect and store information during your use of the Services, including domestic and international audio, web and video conferencing services, live chat, voicemail, audio, web and video recording, voice broadcasting services and other voice and messaging services. In addition, the company may offer other assorted features and applications as part of its Services from time to time. Such in-session information is protected by the use of end-to-end encryption and only accessible to those users you invite, or with whom you otherwise choose to share information. You will have the ability to record, store, and access information related to your use of the Services, and we will not access this information except as may be necessary to support the Services and anticipate, diagnose, or resolve problems that may limit or disrupt the Services, or as may be required by law. Please be aware that any Personal Information you provide to other users during your use of the Services can be collected, used, maintained, shared, or disclosed by those users, and we are not responsible for the collection, use, maintenance, sharing, or disclosure of data and information by such users.

Types of Anonymous Information We Collect
-----------------------------------------

We may also collect and store certain information that does not identify you, such as your Internet protocol address, browser type, domain names and access times (“Anonymous Information”). As you navigate, use, or otherwise interact with the Services, we may use automatic data collection technologies to collect certain information about your equipment and browsing actions, including without limitation: (i) information about your computer or mobile device and internet connection; (ii) details about your visit to the Services, including resources you use on the Services and other traffic, navigational, or communication data; and (iii) your geolocation information. We may also use Cookies (as defined below) and other tracking technologies to collect information about your online activities. "Cookies" are small pieces of information that a website sends to your browser while you are viewing a website. You can instruct your browser, by changing its options, to stop accepting Cookies or to prompt you before accepting a Cookie from the websites you visit. We do not track users across third party websites and therefore do not respond to Do Not Track signals. We may use your Anonymous Information to analyze usage patterns so that we may enhance the Services and improve our internal operations and the content of our software. We may combine such data with certain of your Personal Information.

CarrierX, LLC. complies with all applicable laws regarding data privacy as it pertains to the performance of our services. As part of our compliance we use industry standards to maintain, process, transmit, and store cardholder data on behalf of our customers.

For a list of all permissions requested by CarrierX mobile apps on Android phones, see our [Android Permission](https://www.freeconferencecall.com/android-permissions "Android Permission") document.

How We Use Personal Information
-------------------------------

In general, we may use your Personal Information to:

* Administer your Account and verify your identity;
* Collect your device contacts so you can use your phone book in the virtual phone;
* Process your payments and fulfill your orders;
* Provide you with the Services and customer support;
* Tailor the features, performance, and support of the Services to you;
* Market the Services to you;
* Respond to your requests, resolve disputes, and/or troubleshoot problems;
* Improve the quality of the Services; and
* Communicate with you about the Services.

CarrierX uses email to contact its customers. If you voluntarily submit your email address to receive information, we may subsequently issue Service information to you via email, including technical advisories. Customers receive an initial registration email with all account details listed. After each call, customers receive call detail reports via email. Finally, CarrierX uses email to communicate promotions and product updates with customers (“Promotional Emails”); however, we respect your right to opt out of receiving such Promotional Emails from us. If, at any time after registering, you change your mind about receiving Promotional Emails, you can opt out of receiving such information by sending your request to services@freeconferencecall.com. In addition, you can choose to opt out of the Promotional Emails via the “opt out” link included in each email.

With Whom We Share Personal Information
---------------------------------------

We may disclose your Personal Information: (i) to third party vendors who help us provide the Services, including vendors that help us verify your identity and vendors that process payments for us; (ii) to third parties to whom you ask or authorize us to send Personal Information (including other users) by opting in; (iii) to any subsidiary organizations, joint ventures, or other organizations under our control (collectively, "Affiliates"), in which case we will require our Affiliates to honor this Privacy Statement; (iv) to a company that merges with us, acquires us, or purchases substantially all of our assets, in which case such company may continue to process your Personal Information as set forth in this Privacy Statement; or (v) if we believe in good faith that such disclosure is necessary to: (1) resolve disputes, investigate problems, or enforce our Terms of Service; (2) comply with relevant laws or to respond to requests from law enforcement or other government officials relating to investigations or alleged illegal activity, in which case we can (and you authorize us to) disclose Personal Information without subpoenas or warrants served on us; or (3) protect and defend our rights or property or the rights and property of you or third parties. Except as otherwise stated in this Privacy Policy, we do not trade, rent, or share the Personal Information that we collect with unaffiliated third parties including for their own independent marketing or use.

Third Party Links
-----------------

The Services may contain links to third parties' websites. Please note that we are not responsible for the collection, use, maintenance, sharing, or disclosure of data and information by such third parties. If you provide information on third party sites, the privacy policy and terms of service on those sites are applicable. We encourage you to read the privacy policies of websites that you visit before submitting Personal Information.

California Privacy Policy
-------------------------

California Civil Code Section §1798.83 permits users of our Site that are California residents to request certain information regarding our disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please contact us using the contact information listed below.

Other Information
-----------------

We exercise reasonable security measures to help protect against the loss, misuse, and alteration of your Personal Information. CarrierX hosts its Sites and the collected data in a secure environment that uses reasonable technology to help prevent interference or access from unauthorized persons. Sensitive information that is transmitted to us online (such as credit card number) is encrypted and is transmitted to us securely. Despite such efforts, however, please note that no company, including CarrierX can fully eliminate risks or guarantee the security of your Personal Information; unauthorized entry or use, hardware or software failure, and other factors may compromise the security of information about you at any time. Consequently, we do not guarantee the security of any information you provide to CarrierX through the Sites.

We do not knowingly collect or solicit personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 13. If you are under the age of 13, please do not provide us with any Personal Information. If we learn that we have inadvertently obtained personally identifiable information from a minor under the age of 13, we will delete that information as soon as possible. If you believe that a minor under the age of 13 has submitted Personal Information to us, please contact us using the contact information listed below.

This Privacy Statement is subject to revision from time to time on a going-forward basis. We will post any revised version of the Privacy Statement on this page. If we make any material changes to it, we will also send you notice to the last email address you have provided to us. Continued use of the Services following notice of such changes will indicate your acknowledgement of such changes and agreement to be bound by the terms and conditions of such changes.

For any additional information, or to contact CarrierX, you can email [info@freeconferencecall.com](mailto:info@freeconferencecall.com) or call (844) 844–1322.

* * *

* © FreeConferenceCall.com 2001-2024, ver G

### Americas

Argentina

[Argentina](https://www.freeconferencecall.com/es/ar/privacy-policy "Argentina") _Spanish_

Brazil

[Brazil](https://www.freeconferencecall.com/pt/br/privacy-policy "Brazil") _Portuguese_

Canada

[Canada](https://www.freeconferencecall.com/global/ca/privacy-policy "Canada") _English_

Chile

[Chile](https://www.freeconferencecall.com/es/cl/privacy-policy "Chile") _Spanish_

Colombia

[Colombia](https://www.freeconferencecall.com/es/co/privacy-policy "Colombia") _Spanish_

Costa Rica

[Costa Rica](https://www.freeconferencecall.com/es/cr/privacy-policy "Costa Rica") _Spanish_

Dominican Republic

[Dominican Republic](https://www.freeconferencecall.com/es/do/privacy-policy "Dominican Republic") _Spanish_

Guatemala

[Guatemala](https://www.freeconferencecall.com/es/gt/privacy-policy "Guatemala") _Spanish_

Mexico

[Mexico](https://www.freeconferencecall.com/es/mx/privacy-policy "Mexico") _Spanish_

Panama

[Panama](https://www.freeconferencecall.com/es/pa/privacy-policy "Panama") _Spanish_

Peru

[Peru](https://www.freeconferencecall.com/es/pe/privacy-policy "Peru") _Spanish_

United States

[United States](https://www.freeconferencecall.com/global/us/privacy-policy "United States") _English_

### EMEA

Afghanistan

[Afghanistan](https://www.freeconferencecall.com/global/af/privacy-policy "Afghanistan") _English_

Austria

[Austria](https://www.freeconferencecall.com/de/at/privacy-policy "Austria") _German_

Bahrain

[Bahrain](https://www.freeconferencecall.com/ar/bh/privacy-policy "Bahrain") _Arabic_

Belgium

[Belgium](https://www.freeconferencecall.com/nl/be/privacy-policy "Belgium") _Dutch_

Bosnia and Herzegovina

[Bosnia and Herzegovina](https://www.freeconferencecall.com/global/ba/privacy-policy "Bosnia and Herzegovina") _English_

Bulgaria

[Bulgaria](https://www.freeconferencecall.com/global/bg/privacy-policy "Bulgaria") _English_

Cameroon

[Cameroon](https://www.freeconferencecall.com/fr/cm/privacy-policy "Cameroon") _French_

Croatia

[Croatia](https://www.freeconferencecall.com/global/hr/privacy-policy "Croatia") _English_

Cyprus

[Cyprus](https://www.freeconferencecall.com/global/cy/privacy-policy "Cyprus") _English_

Czech

[Czech](https://www.freeconferencecall.com/global/cz/privacy-policy "Czech Republic") _English_

Denmark

[Denmark](https://www.freeconferencecall.com/da/dk/privacy-policy "Denmark") _Danish_

Estonia

[Estonia](https://www.freeconferencecall.com/global/ee/privacy-policy "Estonia") _English_

Finland

[Finland](https://www.freeconferencecall.com/fi/fi/privacy-policy "Finland") _Finnish_

France

[France](https://www.freeconferencecall.com/fr/fr/privacy-policy "France") _French_

Georgia

[Georgia](https://www.freeconferencecall.com/global/ge/privacy-policy "Georgia") _English_

Germany

[Germany](https://www.freeconferencecall.com/de/de/privacy-policy "Germany") _German_

Greece

[Greece](https://www.freeconferencecall.com/global/gr/privacy-policy "Greece") _English_

Hungary

[Hungary](https://www.freeconferencecall.com/global/hu/privacy-policy "Hungary") _English_

Iceland

[Iceland](https://www.freeconferencecall.com/global/is/privacy-policy "Iceland") _English_

India

[India](https://www.freeconferencecall.com/global/in/privacy-policy "India") _English_

Ireland

[Ireland](https://www.freeconferencecall.com/global/ie/privacy-policy "Ireland") _English_

Italy

[Italy](https://www.freeconferencecall.com/it/it/privacy-policy "Italy") _Italian_

Kazakhstan

[Kazakhstan](https://www.freeconferencecall.com/global/kz/privacy-policy "Kazakhstan") _English_

Kenya

[Kenya](https://www.freeconferencecall.com/global/ke/privacy-policy "Kenya") _English_

Latvia

[Latvia](https://www.freeconferencecall.com/global/lv/privacy-policy "Latvia") _English_

Lithuania

[Lithuania](https://www.freeconferencecall.com/global/lt/privacy-policy "Lithuania") _English_

Luxembourg

[Luxembourg](https://www.freeconferencecall.com/de/lu/privacy-policy "Luxembourg") _German_

Malawi

[Malawi](https://www.freeconferencecall.com/global/mw/privacy-policy "Malawi") _English_

Monaco

[Monaco](https://www.freeconferencecall.com/fr/mc/privacy-policy "Monaco") _French_

Montenegro

[Montenegro](https://www.freeconferencecall.com/global/me/privacy-policy "Montenegro") _English_

Netherlands

[Netherlands](https://www.freeconferencecall.com/nl/nl/privacy-policy "Netherlands") _Dutch_

Nigeria

[Nigeria](https://www.freeconferencecall.com/global/ng/privacy-policy "Nigeria") _English_

Norway

[Norway](https://www.freeconferencecall.com/no/no/privacy-policy "Norway") _Norwegian_

Pakistan

[Pakistan](https://www.freeconferencecall.com/global/pk/privacy-policy "Pakistan") _English_

Poland

[Poland](https://www.freeconferencecall.com/pl/pl/privacy-policy "Poland") _Polish_

Portugal

[Portugal](https://www.freeconferencecall.com/pt/pt/privacy-policy "Portugal") _Portuguese_

Romania

[Romania](https://www.freeconferencecall.com/global/ro/privacy-policy "Romania") _English_

Russian Federation

[Russian Federation](https://www.freeconferencecall.com/ru/ru/privacy-policy "Russian Federation") _Russian_

Serbia

[Serbia](https://www.freeconferencecall.com/global/rs/privacy-policy "Serbia") _English_

Slovakia

[Slovakia](https://www.freeconferencecall.com/global/sk/privacy-policy "Slovakia") _English_

Slovenia

[Slovenia](https://www.freeconferencecall.com/global/si/privacy-policy "Slovenia") _English_

South Africa

[South Africa](https://www.freeconferencecall.com/global/za/privacy-policy "South Africa") _English_

Spain

[Spain](https://www.freeconferencecall.com/es/es/privacy-policy "Spain") _Spanish_

Sri Lanka

[Sri Lanka](https://www.freeconferencecall.com/global/lk/privacy-policy "Sri Lanka") _English_

Sweden

[Sweden](https://www.freeconferencecall.com/sv/se/privacy-policy "Sweden") _Swedish_

Switzerland

[Switzerland](https://www.freeconferencecall.com/de/ch/privacy-policy "Switzerland") _German_

Turkey

[Turkey](https://www.freeconferencecall.com/tr/tr/privacy-policy "Turkey") _Turkish_

Uganda

[Uganda](https://www.freeconferencecall.com/global/ug/privacy-policy "Uganda") _English_

Ukraine

[Ukraine](https://www.freeconferencecall.com/global/ua/privacy-policy "Ukraine") _English_

United Arab Emirates

[United Arab Emirates](https://www.freeconferencecall.com/ar/ae/privacy-policy "United Arab Emirates") _Arabic_

United Kingdom

[United Kingdom](https://www.freeconferencecall.com/global/gb/privacy-policy "United Kingdom") _English_

### Asia Pacific

Australia

[Australia](https://www.freeconferencecall.com/global/au/privacy-policy "Australia") _English_

Cambodia

[Cambodia](https://www.freeconferencecall.com/global/kh/privacy-policy "Cambodia") _English_

China

[China](https://www.freeconferencecall.com/zh/cn/privacy-policy "China") _Mandarin_

Hong Kong

[Hong Kong](https://www.freeconferencecall.com/global/hk/privacy-policy "Hong Kong") _English_

Indonesia

[Indonesia](https://www.freeconferencecall.com/global/id/privacy-policy "Indonesia") _English_

Japan

[Japan](https://www.freeconferencecall.com/ja/jp/privacy-policy "Japan") _Japanese_

Mongolia

[Mongolia](https://www.freeconferencecall.com/global/mn/privacy-policy "Mongolia") _English_

New Zealand

[New Zealand](https://www.freeconferencecall.com/global/nz/privacy-policy "New Zealand") _English_

Philippines

[Philippines](https://www.freeconferencecall.com/global/ph/privacy-policy "Philippines") _English_

Taiwan

[Taiwan](https://www.freeconferencecall.com/global/tw/privacy-policy "Taiwan") _English_

Thailand

[Thailand](https://www.freeconferencecall.com/global/th/privacy-policy "Thailand") _English_

Vietnam

[Vietnam](https://www.freeconferencecall.com/global/vn/privacy-policy "Vietnam") _English_

Close

#### Recommendation

For the best user experience we recommend that you upgrade your browser using the provided links below.

[Chrome  
Google](https://www.google.com/chrome/browser/desktop/ "Google Chrome")

[Firefox  
Mozilla Foundation](https://www.mozilla.com/firefox/ "Firefox")

[Edge  
Microsoft](https://www.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/microsoft-edge "Microsoft Edge")

[Safari  
Apple](https://www.apple.com/safari/ "Safari")

I understand it may not be compatible continue using this browser
